Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Argentina (1969-1974) File, 1966-1975 (Boxes 186-213)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1975
    - Benfield, James W., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 196: 47)
    - Benton, Mr. and Mrs. William, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 196: 48)
    - Bishop, Max, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 196: 49)
    - Black, Shirley Temple, 1972 (Box-folder 196: 50)
    - Bliss, Robert, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 196: 51)
    - Bobich, Gica, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 196: 52)
    - Bobst, Elmer, 1969 (Box-folder 196: 53)
    - Bockstoce, Mrs. Clifton, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 196: 54)
    - Bodisco, Aino de, 1969 (Box-folder 196: 55)
    - Bohlen, Charles, 1972 (Box-folder 196: 56)
    - Boit, Julian, 1972 (Box-folder 196: 57)
    - Bolton, Frances, 1973 (Box-folder 196: 58)
    - Bolton-Smith, Carlile, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 196: 59)
    - Borbon y Orleans, Alfonso, 1971 (Box-folder 196: 60)
    - Boriecha, Jacqueline, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 197: 1)
    - Boyd, John, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 2)
    - Braden, Spruille, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 197: 3)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 197: 4)
    - Braggiotti, Mario, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 5)
    - Braggiotti, Rama, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 197: 6)
    - Brouilette, C. Bader, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 197: 7)
    - Brown, John C., 1970 (Box-folder 197: 8)
    - Brown, Mrs. John Mason, undated (Box-folder 197: 9)
    - Brownell, Herbert, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 10)
    - Buchanan, Wiley, Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 197: 11)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 12)
    - Bullock, Hugh, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 197: 13)
    - Bundy, Mrs. McGeorge, 1970 (Box-folder 197: 14)
    - Burden, William A. M., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 197: 15)
    - Burgess, Carter, 1970 (Box-folder 197: 16)
    - Burgess, Randolph, 1969 (Box-folder 197: 17)
    - Burke, Arleigh, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 197: 18)
    - Burke, Gerard, 1972 (Box-folder 197: 19)
    - Burns, Arthur F., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 197: 20)
    - Bush, George, 1970 (Box-folder 197: 21)
    - Bush, Prescott, 1972 (Box-folder 197: 22)
    - Bustillo, Joaquin, 1973 (Box-folder 197: 23)
    - Butterfield, Alexander, 1972 (Box-folder 197: 24)
    - Byington, Homer, Jr., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 197: 25)
    - Byrnes, John W., 1972 (Box-folder 197: 26)
    - Cabot, Thomas, 1971 (Box-folder 197: 27)
    - Capitol Hill Club, 1971 (Box-folder 197: 28)
    - Capitol Hill Foundation, 1971 (Box-folder 197: 29)
    - Carcano, Miguel, 1973 (Box-folder 197: 30)
    - Carey, Charles T., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 31)
    - Carleton, Peter, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 197: 32)
    - Casas Ledesma, Frances, 1970 (Box-folder 197: 33)
    - Castiella, Fernando M., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 34)
    - Cerlanek, Francis, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 197: 35)
    - Chaisson, Mrs. John, 1972 (Box-folder 197: 36)
    - Chapuis, Jeanne, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 197: 37)
    - Chennault, Anna, 1969 (Box-folder 197: 38)
    - Cholmeley-Jones, E. O. Nigel, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 197: 39)
    - Choquette, Robert, 1970 (Box-folder 197: 40)
    - Chotiner, Murray, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 197: 41)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 42)
    - Cole, Sterling, 1973 (Box-folder 197: 43)
    - Committee to End Aid to the Soviet Enemy (C.E.A.S.E.), 1969 (Box-folder 197: 44)
    - Conant, Luther, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 197: 45)
    - Cook, Joseph, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 197: 46)
    - Coote, Albert, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 47)
    - Corry, Andrew, 1969 (Box-folder 197: 48)
    - Cotton, Helen, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 198: 1)
    - Courdet, Mrs. Frederic, 1972 (Box-folder 198: 2)
    - Coward, Noel, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 3)
    - Crane, Kent, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 4)
    - Crisler, Richard C., 1971 (Box-folder 198: 5)
    - Crittenberger, W. D., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 6)
    - Crocker, Lispenard, 1971 (Box-folder 198: 7)
    - Crowley, John, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 8)
    - Cupelli, Alberto, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 9)
    - Cushman, Charles van B., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 198: 10)
    - Daniel, Margaret (Truman), 1973 (Box-folder 198: 11)
    - Davenport, Russell, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 12)
    - Davis, Fitzroy, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 13)
    - Davis, Glenn R., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 14)
    - Davis, Nathaniel, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 198: 15)
    - Davis, Shelby C., 1971-1973 (Box-folder 198: 16)
    - Dempsey, John, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 17)
    - Dewart, Thomas, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 198: 18)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., undated (Box-folder 198: 19)
    - Dirksen, Everett, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 20)
    - Dodd, Thomas, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 21)
    - Dohanos, Steve, 1972 (Box-folder 198: 22)
    - Donovan, Mrs. Stanley, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 198: 23)
    - Douglas-Hamilton, Malcolm, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 24)
    - Drouin, Jacques, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 25)
    - Dudley, Henry, 1972 (Box-folder 198: 26)
    - Dugan, Jonathan, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 198: 27)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1971 (Box-folder 198: 28)
    - Dymkoski, Leo, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 29)
    - Eames, Hamilton, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 30)
    - Egan, John J., 1971 (Box-folder 198: 31)
    - Ehrlichman, John D., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 32)
    - Eisenhower, Mr. and Mrs. David, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 33)
    - Eisenhower, John, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 34)
    - Eisenhower, Mamie, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 35)
    - Eisenhower, Milton, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 36)
    - Elbrick, C. Burke, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 37)
    - Ellinger, John, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 38)
    - Elston, Dorothy, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 39)
    - Espil, Mr. and Mrs. Felipe, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 40)
    - Estes, Thomas, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 198: 41)
    - Estrella, Evelio, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 42)
    - Etienne, Walter O., 1970 (Box-folder 198: 43)
    - Etting, Mr. and Mrs. Emlen, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 44)
    - Evans, Thomas W., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 45)
    - Fairfield County Hunt Club, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 46)
    - Farley, James A., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 47)
    - Feisal, Alfred, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 198: 48)
    - Ferne, Luis A., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 49)
    - Field, David J., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 50)
    - Filosa, Gary F., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 51)
    - Fish, Hamilton, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 198: 52)
    - Fitzpatrick, John, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 53)
    - Flack, Anthony H., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 54)
    - Flanigan, Peter, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 55)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 56)
    - Forster, Percy, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 57)
    - Forte, Ralph E., 1972 (Box-folder 198: 58)
    - Fox Club, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 59)
    - Fraleigh, William, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 60)
    - Francoeur, Philip, 1972 (Box-folder 198: 61)
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 62)
    - Frisby, Owen, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 63)
    - Fulton, James G., 1971 (Box-folder 198: 64)
    - Gabard, Mrs. Pierre, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 65)
    - Garcia Garcia, Gabriel, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 66)
    - Garrigues, Walker, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 198: 67)
    - Gates, Thomas S., 1969 (Box-folder 198: 68)
    - Gelardin, Albert, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 69)
    - Gerety, Pierce, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 70)
    - Gibson, George, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 71)
    - Gimbel, Bernard, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 72)
    - Godo, Conde de, 1970 (Box-folder 198: 73)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 198: 74)
    - Graham, Kay, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 198: 75)
    - Grand, Stanley, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 198: 76)
    - Grandville, Jean de la, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 198: 77)
    - Granville, W. Irving, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 198: 78)
    - Grasso, Ella, 1971 (Box-folder 198: 79)
    - Gray, Francis, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 80)
    - Greffet, Charles, 1971 (Box-folder 198: 81)
    - Gutierrez de Tobar, Javier, 1969 (Box-folder 198: 82)
    - Hadow, Michael, 1971 (Box-folder 199: 1)
    - Hagan, Joseph P., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 199: 2)
    - Hamilton, Natalie Wales, 1973 (Box-folder 199: 3)
    - Harlow, Bryce, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 4)
    - Hart, Thomas C., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 199: 5)
    - Harvard Club, 1970 (Box-folder 199: 6)
    - Hatch, Alden, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 199: 7)
    - Haugh, John, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 199: 8)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1972 (Box-folder 199: 9)
    - Helen, Queen Mother of Rumania, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 10)
    - Hendelson, William, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 11)
    - Henry, Isabella, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 199: 12)
    - Herod, William Rogers, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 13)
    - Hickling, R. A., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 199: 14)
    - Hicks, Ira, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 15)
    - Hidalgo, Edward, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 16)
    - Hill, Robert C., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 17-18)
    - Hillings, Patrick, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 199: 19)
    - Hilson, Mrs. Edwin, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 20)
    - Hilson, John, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 199: 21)
    - Hirsch, Herbert, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 199: 22)
    - Hirsh, Mario, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 199: 23)
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 199: 24)
    - Holtzmann, Fanny E., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 25)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 199: 26)
    - Hotchkis, Preston, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 199: 27)
    - Houghton, James R., 1971 (Box-folder 199: 28)
    - House, Charles, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 199: 29)
    - Houston, Howard, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 199: 30)
    - Hudson Institute, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 199: 31)
    - Hungarian Freedom Fighters, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 32)
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1973 (Box-folder 199: 33)
    - Iribarne, Manuel Fraga, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 34)
    - Ives, Colin, 1971 (Box-folder 199: 35)
    - Jackson, Donald, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 36)
    - Janis, Martin, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 37)
    - Jarrell, Henry, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 199: 38)
    - Javits, Benjamin, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 39)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1970 (Box-folder 199: 40)
    - Johnson, Mr. and Mrs. Lyndon B., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 199: 41)
    - Jones, Jenkin Lloyd, 1970 (Box-folder 199: 42)
    - Jova, Joseph, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 199: 43)
    - Juan de Borbon, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 199: 44)
    - Kandarian, Everett, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 45)
    - Kaufmann, Arthur, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 46)
    - Kearns, Henry, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 199: 47)
    - Keating, Kenneth, 1973 (Box-folder 199: 48)
    - Kelly, Joseph, 1970 (Box-folder 199: 49)
    - Kemper, Alfred, 1970 (Box-folder 199: 50)
    - Kennedy, Dana, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 199: 51)
    - Kilgallon, William, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 52)
    - Kimball, Jeffrey, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 199: 53)
    - Kimball, John M., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 199: 54)
    - Kintner, William R., 1973 (Box-folder 200: 1)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 200: 2)
    - Klein, Herbert G., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 200: 3)
    - Kleindienst, Richard, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 4)
    - Klemann, George, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 200: 5)
    - Kluckhohn, Frank, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 200: 6)
    - Knopf, Alfred, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 7)
    - Koopmans, Willem, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 200: 8)
    - Krebs, A. Samuel, 1973 (Box-folder 200: 9)
    - Kriendler, John, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 200: 10)
    - Kriendler, Maxwell, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 200: 11)
    - Kreisler, Ed, 1969 (Box-folder 200: 12)
    - Krueger, Ernest G., 1972 (Box-folder 200: 13)
    - Kubisch, Jack B., 1973 (Box-folder 200: 14)
    - Laird, Melvin, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 15)
    - Lamont, Mr. and Mrs. Gordon, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 16)
    - Larrabee, Donald, 1972 (Box-folder 200: 17)
    - Law, Marion, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 200: 18)
    - Leddy, Raymond, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 200: 19)
    - Leigh, Elsie, 1972 (Box-folder 200: 20)
    - Levy, Hermann, 1969 (Box-folder 200: 21)
    - Lewis, Marx, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 200: 22)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1969 (Box-folder 200: 23)
    - Llambi, Benito, 1973 (Box-folder 200: 24)
    - Loder, John, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 200: 25)
    - Lodge, Francesca, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 200: 26)
    - Lodge, George C., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 200: 27)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 28)
    - Lodge, Mrs. John E., 1970 (Box-folder 200: 29)
    - Loeb, William, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 200: 30)
    - Loomis, Patricia, 1973 (Box-folder 200: 31)
    - Lopez Moya, Fernando, 1970 (Box-folder 200: 32)
    - Lopez Rodo, Laureano, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 200: 33)
    - Lord, Charles, 1972 (Box-folder 200: 34)
    - Loy, Mrs. Thomas, 1969 (Box-folder 200: 35)
    - Luca de Tena, Juan I., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 200: 36)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1969 (Box-folder 200: 37)
    - Lupton, John M., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 200: 38)
    - Macarelli, Ralph, 1971 (Box-folder 200: 39)
    - MacArthur, Helen Hays, 1970 (Box-folder 200: 40)
    - Macaya, Ignacio, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 200: 41)
    - McBride, Robert, 1970 (Box-folder 200: 42)
    - McClintock, Robert M., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 200: 43)
    - McEvoy, Joseph, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 201: 1)
    - McGregor, Clark, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 201: 2)
    - McGuire, Perkins, 1969 (Box-folder 201: 3)
    - Mackay, Helen, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 201: 4)
    - McNeil, Thomas J., 1971 (Box-folder 201: 5)
    - Madariaga, Juan Jose de, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 6)
    - Males, L., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 7)
    - Marcus, Lily Lodge and James, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 8-9)
    - Martin, Ralph, 1973 (Box-folder 201: 10)
    - Martin-Gamero, Adolfo, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 201: 11)
    - Mason, Anne, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 201: 12)
    - Maury, Reuben, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 201: 13)
    - Meloy, Francis E., Jr., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 201: 14)
    - Merry del Val, Alfonso, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 201: 15)
    - Meskill, Thomas, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 201: 16)
    - Mestre, Goar, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 201: 17)
    - Meyer, Charles, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 201: 18)
    - Meyer, Fleur, 1971 (Box-folder 201: 19)
    - Michel, Robert, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 201: 20)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 21)
    - Middlesex School, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 22)
    - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 23)
    - Miller, William J., 1969 (Box-folder 201: 24)
    - Misch, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 1973 (Box-folder 201: 25)
    - Mitchell, John D., 1972 (Box-folder 201: 26)
    - Mitchell, John N., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 27)
    - Montllor, Joseph, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 201: 28)
    - Morano, Albert P., 1970 (Box-folder 201: 29)
    - Morris, Suzy, 1969 (Box-folder 201: 30)
    - Mortensen, William, 1971 (Box-folder 201: 31)
    - Morton, Rogers C. B., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 201: 32)
    - Mosher, Byron K., 1971 (Box-folder 201: 33)
    - Mott, Jordan L., III, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 201: 34)
    - Mundt, Karl, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 201: 35)
    - Munoz, Antonio, 1969 (Box-folder 201: 36)
    - Muns, Alejandro de, 1973 (Box-folder 201: 37)
    - Muse, Martha, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 201: 38)
    - Napper, Bernice, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 39)
    - Nash, Edward, 1970 (Box-folder 201: 40)
    - Neal, Jack, 1969 (Box-folder 201: 41)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 201: 42, 202: 1)
    - Nixon, Tricia, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 202: 2)
    - Noble, Ernestina, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 202: 3)
    - Noel, Sterling, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 202: 4)
    - Nonancourt, Bernard, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 5)
    - Norton, Josiah, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 6)
    - Norton, Julian, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 7)
    - Nyardi, Nicholas, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 202: 8)
    - Oakie, Mr. and Mrs. Jack, 1973 (Box-folder 202: 9)
    - O'Connor, George, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 202: 10)
    - Olano, Luis de, 1972 (Box-folder 202: 11)
    - Olivera, Pablo, 1970 (Box-folder 202: 12)
    - Oram, Frank, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 202: 13)
    - Orlandini, Elizabeth, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 202: 14)
    - Ortiz, Frank, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 202: 15)
    - Ortano, Egido, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 16)
    - Oyarzabal, Beatrice Lodge and Antonio de, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 202: 17)
    - Padilla, 1972 (Box-folder 202: 18)
    - Pan American Society of the United States, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 19)
    - Pappas, Thomas, 1972 (Box-folder 202: 20)
    - Parker, David, 1972 (Box-folder 202: 21)
    - Parr, Charles, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 22)
    - Pawley, William D., 1970 (Box-folder 202: 23)
    - Pell, John H. G., 1969 (Box-folder 202: 24)
    - Pinies, Jaime de, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 202: 25)
    - Ploeser, Walter, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 202: 26)
    - Pogany, Andras, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 27)
    - Presbury, Martha, 1970 (Box-folder 202: 28)
    - Pryor, Samuel, 1971 (Box-folder 202: 29)
    - Quilleret, Pierre, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 30)
    - Quincy, Edmund, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 202: 31)
    - Quintanilla, Aline, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 202: 32)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 196? (Box-folder 202: 33)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1970 (Box-folder 202: 34)
    - Reincke, F. G., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 202: 35)
    - Reinhardt, Frederick, 1971 (Box-folder 202: 36)
    - Reitmeyer, John, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 202: 37)
    - Rentschler, George, 1972 (Box-folder 202: 38)
    - Reynolds, Reginald, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 202: 39)
    - Republican National Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 202: 40)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 1)
    - Richardson, Elliott, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 2)
    - Riddleberger, James W., 1969 (Box-folder 203: 3)
    - Rimanoczy, Richard S., 1973 (Box-folder 203: 4)
    - Roca, Alejandro, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 5)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1972 (Box-folder 203: 6)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 7)
    - Rogers, William P., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 8)
    - Rooney, John J., 1970 (Box-folder 203: 9)
    - Roosevelt, Archibald, Jr., 1970 (Box-folder 203: 10)
    - Roots, John McCook, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 203: 11)
    - Rosoff, Samuel, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 12)
    - Roth, Philip, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 13)
    - Rothblum, E. G., 1969 (Box-folder 203: 14)
    - Rubottom, R. Richard, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 203: 15)
    - Ruiz Padilla, Manuel, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 16)
    - Rysdyk, Frank, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 17)
    - Saccio, Leonard, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 18)
    - Sacksteder, Frederick, Jr., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 19)
    - Sadlak, Antoni, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 20)
    - Safire, William, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 21)
    - Salas Lopez, Fernando, 1972 (Box-folder 203: 22)
    - Salles, Edouard, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 203: 23)
    - Sampsell, Marshall, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 203: 24)
    - Sans Mora, Miguel, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 25)
    - Sanz-Briz, Angel, 1970 (Box-folder 203: 26)
    - Sargent, Noel, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 27)
    - Savitt, Max, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 28)
    - Saxe, Tom, 1970 (Box-folder 203: 29)
    - Schlanger, Irving, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 203: 30)
    - Schonburg, Count Rudi von, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 203: 31)
    - Schwolsky, Harry, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 32)
    - Scott, Hugh, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 33)
    - Seawell, W. T., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 203: 34)
    - Shakespeare, Frank, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 35)
    - Sharp, Dudley, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 203: 36)
    - Shaw, Alejandro, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 37)
    - Sidor, Walter, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 38)
    - Sill, Fred, 1971 (Box-folder 203: 39)
    - Smedberg, William R., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 40)
    - Smith, Carleton S., 1969 (Box-folder 203: 41)
    - Smith, David S., 1969 (Box-folder 203: 42)
    - Spanish Institute, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 43)
    - Speaks, Charles, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 203: 44)
    - Speiden, Jack, 1970 (Box-folder 203: 45)
    - St. Albans School, 1972 (Box-folder 203: 46)
    - Stahl, Frederick, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 203: 47)
    - Stalker, Hugh, 1970 (Box-folder 203: 48)
    - Stans, Maurice, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 203: 49)
    - Steele, Robert H., 1973 (Box-folder 203: 50)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 51)
    - Stewart, John E., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 203: 52)
    - Stilson, Germaine, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 53)
    - Stolpen, Adam, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 54)
    - Stone, Lewis A., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 203: 55)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 203: 56)
    - Streel, Quentin de, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 203: 57)
    - Streel, Helena Lodge de, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 203: 58)
    - Sueca, Duque and Duquesa de, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 203: 59)
    - Sullivan, Peter B., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 203: 60)
    - Sulzberger, C.L., 1971 (Box-folder 203: 61)
    - Symington, J. Fife, Jr., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 203: 62)
    - Symington, James, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 1)
    - Symington, Stuart, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 2)
    - Szechenyi, C. A., 1970 (Box-folder 204: 3)
    - Tate, Margot, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 204: 4)
    - Taylor and Schlanger, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 204: 5)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1972 (Box-folder 204: 6)
    - Taylor, Lorenzo, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 7)
    - Terry, Carroll M., 1972 (Box-folder 204: 8)
    - Tettamanti, Leopoldo H., undated (Box-folder 204: 9)
    - Thompson, Herbert, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 10)
    - Thorndike, Benjamin, 1972 (Box-folder 204: 11)
    - Thorning, Joseph, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 204: 12)
    - Tinker Foundation, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 13)
    - Toledo, Dagmar Alvarez de, 1973 (Box-folder 204: 14)
    - Tournelle, Guy, 1973 (Box-folder 204: 15)
    - Townsend, Earle, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 16)
    - Tripp, Wendell, 1972 (Box-folder 204: 17)
    - Trohan, Walter, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 18)
    - Truman, Mrs. Harry S., 1973 (Box-folder 204: 19)
    - Tunney, Gene, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 20)
    - Turner, Arthur, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 204: 21)
    - Turner, Frederick C., 1973 (Box-folder 204: 22)
    - Unander, Sigfried, 1971 (Box-folder 204: 23)
    - Valenti, Jack, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 24)
    - Van de Vere, Lillian, 1969 (Box-folder 204: 25)
    - Vega, Matias, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 26)
    - Villalon, Luis, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 27)
    - Volodine, George A., 1972 (Box-folder 204: 28)
    - Volpe, John A., 1973 (Box-folder 204: 29)
    - Von Sternberg, Mrs. Joseph, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 30)
    - Wadsworth, James J., 1973 (Box-folder 204: 31)
    - Walker, John W., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 204: 32)
    - Watson, Zetta J., 1972 (Box-folder 204: 33)
    - Watt, Raymond, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 34)
    - Watts, Henry M., Jr., 1969 (Box-folder 204: 35)
    - Waugh, Albert, 1971 (Box-folder 204: 36)
    - Waugh, Samuel, 1969 (Box-folder 204: 37)
    - Weicker, Lowell, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 204: 38)
    - Weiss, Gaspard, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 39)
    - Whelan, Richard, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 40)
    - Whitehouse, Mrs. Brooks, 1969 (Box-folder 204: 41)
    - Whitney, John Hay, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 42)
    - Wide World Lecture Bureau, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 43)
    - Will, Admiral John M., 1971 (Box-folder 204: 44)
    - Williams, Ed, 1973 (Box-folder 204: 45)
    - Williams, Paul W., 1969-1972 (Box-folder 204: 46)
    - Wilson, Bob, 1971 (Box-folder 204: 47)
    - Wold, John S., 1969 (Box-folder 204: 48)
    - Wood, Allen, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 204: 49)
    - Woodbridge, Henry, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 50)
    - Woods, Rose Mary, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 204: 51)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, undated (Box-folder 204: 52)
    - Zaiman, Jack, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 204: 53)
    - Zanini, Lino, 1973 (Box-folder 204: 54)
    - Ziegler, Ronald, 1973 (Box-folder 204: 55)
    - Ziluca, Giuseppina Garibaldi, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 56)
    - Ziluca, Paul, 1970 (Box-folder 204: 57)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R., Jr., 1971 (Box-folder 204: 58)
  - Office file, 1969-1973, undated
    - General (Box-folder 204: 59)
    - Deputy Chief of Mission (Max Krebs) (Box-folder 205: 1)
    - Visit of Charles Meyer, Assistant Secretary of State (Box-folder 205: 2)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 205: 3)
    - Memoranda (Box-folder 205: 4)
    - Travel file
      - 1969
        - Balcarce (Box-folder 205: 5)
        - Mexico (Box-folder 205: 6)